<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><compendium version="5" auto_indent="YES">
	<item>		<name>Arrow of Slaying</name>		<type>A</type>		<weight>0.05</weight>		<text>	An arrow of slaying is a magic weapon meant to slay a particular kind of creature. Some are more focused than others; for example, there are both arrows of dragon slaying and arrows of blue dragon slaying. If a creature belonging to the type, race, or group associated with an arrow of slaying takes damage from the arrow, the creature must make a DC 17 Constitution saving throw, taking an extra 6d10 piercing damage on a failed save, or half as much extra damage on a successful one.</text>		<text>Once an arrow of slaying deals its extra damage to a creature, it becomes a nonmagical arrow.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 152</text>		<roll>6d10</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Blowgun Needle of Slaying</name>		<type>A</type>		<weight>0.02</weight>		<text>	A blowgun needle of slaying is a magic weapon meant to slay a particular kind of creature. Some are more focused than others; for example, there are both needles of dragon slaying and needles of blue dragon slaying. If a creature belonging to the type, race, or group associated with a needle of slaying takes damage from the needle the creature must make a DC 17 Constitution saving throw, taking an extra 6d10 piercing damage on a failed save, or half as much extra damage on a successful one.</text>		<text>Once a needle of slaying deals its extra damage to a creature, it becomes a nonmagical blowgun needle.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 152</text>		<roll>6d10</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Crossbow Bolt of Slaying</name>		<type>A</type>		<weight>0.075</weight>		<text>	A crossbow bolt of slaying is a magic weapon meant to slay a particular kind of creature. Some are more focused than others; for example, there are both bolts of dragon slaying and bolts of blue dragon slaying. If a creature belonging to the type, race, or group associated with a bolt of slaying takes damage from the bolt the creature must make a DC 17 Constitution saving throw, taking an extra 6d10 piercing damage on a failed save, or half as much extra damage on a successful one.</text>		<text>Once a bolt of slaying deals its extra damage to a creature, it becomes a nonmagical crossbow bolt.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 152</text>		<roll>6d10</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Sling Bullet of Slaying</name>		<type>A</type>		<weight>0.075</weight>		<text>	A sling bullet of slaying is a magic weapon meant to slay a particular kind of creature. Some are more focused than others; for example, there are both bullets of dragon slaying and bullets of blue dragon slaying. If a creature belonging to the type, race, or group associated with a bullet of slaying takes damage from the bullet the creature must make a DC 17 Constitution saving throw, taking an extra 6d10 piercing damage on a failed save, or half as much extra damage on a successful one.</text>		<text>Once a bullet of slaying deals its extra damage to a creature, it becomes a nonmagical sling bullet.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 152</text>		<roll>6d10</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Armor of Invulnerability</name>		<type>HA</type>		<weight>65</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You have resistance to nonmagical damage while you wear this armor. Additionally, you can use an action to make yourself immune to nonmagical damage for 10 minutes or until you are no longer wearing the armor. Once this special action is used, it can't be used again until the next dawn.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 152</text>		<ac>18</ac>		<strength>15</strength>		<stealth>1</stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Armor of Vulnerability (Bludgeoning)</name>		<type>HA</type>		<weight>65</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	While wearing this armor, you have resistance to bludgeoning damage.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: This armor is cursed, a fact that is revealed only when an identify spell is cast on the armor or you attune to it. Attuning to the armor curses you until you are targeted by the remove curse spell or similar magic; removing the armor fails to end the curse. While cursed you have vulnerability to piercing and slashing damage.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 152</text>		<ac>18</ac>		<strength>15</strength>		<stealth>1</stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Armor of Vulnerability (Piercing)</name>		<type>HA</type>		<weight>65</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	While wearing this armor, you have resistance to piercing damage.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: This armor is cursed, a fact that is revealed only when an identify spell is cast on the armor or you attune to it. Attuning to the armor curses you until you are targeted by the remove curse spell or similar magic; removing the armor fails to end the curse. While cursed you have vulnerability to bludgeoning and slashing damage.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 152</text>		<ac>18</ac>		<strength>15</strength>		<stealth>1</stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Armor of Vulnerability (Slashing)</name>		<type>HA</type>		<weight>65</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	While wearing this armor, you have resistance to slashing damage.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: This armor is cursed, a fact that is revealed only when an identify spell is cast on the armor or you attune to it. Attuning to the armor curses you until you are targeted by the remove curse spell or similar magic; removing the armor fails to end the curse. While cursed you have vulnerability to bludgeoning and piercing damage.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 152</text>		<ac>18</ac>		<strength>15</strength>		<stealth>1</stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Demon Armor</name>		<type>HA</type>		<weight>65</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	While wearing this armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC, and you can understand and speak Abyssal. In addition, the armor's clawed gauntlets turn unarmed strikes with your hands into magic weapons that deal slashing damage, with a +1 bonus to attack rolls and damage rolls and a damage die of 1d8.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: Once you don this cursed armor, you can't doff it unless you are targeted by the remove curse spell or similar magic. While wearing the armor, you have disadvantage on attack rolls against demons and on saving throws against their spells and special abilities.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 165</text>		<modifier category="bonus">ac +1</modifier>		<ac>18</ac>		<strength>15</strength>		<stealth>1</stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dwarven Plate</name>		<type>HA</type>		<weight>65</weight>		<text>	While wearing this armor, you gain a +2 bonus to AC. In addition, if an effect moves you against your will along the ground, you can use your reaction to reduce the distance you are moved by up to 10 feet.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 167</text>		<modifier category="bonus">ac +2</modifier>		<ac>18</ac>		<strength>15</strength>		<stealth>1</stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Efreeti Chain</name>		<type>HA</type>		<weight>55</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	While wearing this armor, you gain a +3 bonus to AC, you are immune to fire damage, and you can understand and speak Primordial. In addition, you can stand on and walk across molten rock as if it were solid ground.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 167</text>		<modifier category="bonus">ac +3</modifier>		<ac>16</ac>		<strength>13</strength>		<stealth>1</stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Plate Armor of Etherealness</name>		<type>HA</type>		<weight>65</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	While you're wearing this armor, you can speak its command word as an action to gain the effect of the etherealness spell, which last for 10 minutes or until you remove the armor or use an action to speak the command word again. This property of the armor can't be used again until the next dawn.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 185</text>		<ac>18</ac>		<strength>15</strength>		<stealth>1</stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Glamoured Studded Leather</name>		<type>LA</type>		<weight>12</weight>		<text>	While wearing this armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC. You can also use a bonus action to speak the armor's command word and cause the armor to assume the appearance of a normal set of clothing or some other kind of armor. You decide what it looks like, including color, style, and accessories, but the armor retains its normal bulk and weight. The illusory appearance last until you use this property again or remove the armor.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 172</text>		<modifier category="bonus">ac +1</modifier>		<ac>13</ac>		<strength></strength>		<stealth></stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Berserker Battleaxe</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>4</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. In addition, while you are attuned to this weapon, your hit point maximum increases by 1 for each level you have attained.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: This axe is cursed, and becoming attuned to it extends the curse to you. As long as you remain cursed, you are unwilling to part with the axe, keeping it within reach at all times. You also have disadvantage on attack rolls with weapons other than this one, unless no foe is within 60 feet of you that you can see or hear.</text>		<text>Whenever a hostile creature damages you while the axe is in your possession, you must succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw or go berserk. While berserk, you must use your action each round to attack the creature nearest to you with the axe. If you can make extra attacks as part of the Attack action, you use those extra attacks, moving to attack the next nearest creature after you fell your current target. If you have multiple possible targets, you attack one at random. You are berserk until you start your turn with no creatures within 60 feet of you that you can see or hear.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 155</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Berserker Greataxe</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>7</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. In addition, while you are attuned to this weapon, your hit point maximum increases by 1 for each level you have attained.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: This axe is cursed, and becoming attuned to it extends the curse to you. As long as you remain cursed, you are unwilling to part with the axe, keeping it within reach at all times. You also have disadvantage on attack rolls with weapons other than this one, unless no foe is within 60 feet of you that you can see or hear.</text>		<text>Whenever a hostile creature damages you while the axe is in your possession, you must succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw or go berserk. While berserk, you must use your action each round to attack the creature nearest to you with the axe. If you can make extra attacks as part of the Attack action, you use those extra attacks, moving to attack the next nearest creature after you fell your current target. If you have multiple possible targets, you attack one at random. You are berserk until you start your turn with no creatures within 60 feet of you that you can see or hear.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 155</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d12</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Berserker Handaxe</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. In addition, while you are attuned to this weapon, your hit point maximum increases by 1 for each level you have attained.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: This axe is cursed, and becoming attuned to it extends the curse to you. As long as you remain cursed, you are unwilling to part with the axe, keeping it within reach at all times. You also have disadvantage on attack rolls with weapons other than this one, unless no foe is within 60 feet of you that you can see or hear.</text>		<text>Whenever a hostile creature damages you while the axe is in your possession, you must succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw or go berserk. While berserk, you must use your action each round to attack the creature nearest to you with the axe. If you can make extra attacks as part of the Attack action, you use those extra attacks, moving to attack the next nearest creature after you fell your current target. If you have multiple possible targets, you attack one at random. You are berserk until you start your turn with no creatures within 60 feet of you that you can see or hear.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Range: A weapon that can be used to make a ranged attack has a range shown in parentheses after the ammunition or thrown property. The range lists two numbers. The first is the weapon's normal range in feet, and the second indicates the weapon's maximum range. When attacking a target beyond normal range, you have disadvantage on the attack roll. You can't attack a target beyond the weapon's long range.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Thrown: If a weapon has the thrown property, you can throw the weapon to make a ranged attack. If the weapon is a melee weapon, you use the same ability modifier for that attack roll and damage roll that you would use for a melee attack with the weapon. For example, if you throw a handaxe, you use your Strength, but if you throw a dagger, you can use either your Strength or your Dexterity, since the dagger has the finesse property.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 155</text>		<modifier category="bonus">weapon attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">weapon damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>L,T</property>		<range>20/60</range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dagger of Venom</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>1</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. </text>		<text>You can use an action to cause thick, black poison to coat the blade. The poison remains for 1 minute or until an attack using this weapon hits a creature. That creature must succeed on a DC 15 Constitution saving throw or take 2d10 poison damage and become poisoned for 1 minute. The dagger can't be used this way again until the next dawn.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Range: A weapon that can be used to make a ranged attack has a range shown in parentheses after the ammunition or thrown property. The range lists two numbers. The first is the weapon's normal range in feet, and the second indicates the weapon's maximum range. When attacking a target beyond normal range, you have disadvantage on the attack roll. You can't attack a target beyond the weapon's long range.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Thrown: If a weapon has the thrown property, you can throw the weapon to make a ranged attack. If the weapon is a melee weapon, you use the same ability modifier for that attack roll and damage roll that you would use for a melee attack with the weapon. For example, if you throw a handaxe, you use your Strength, but if you throw a dagger, you can use either your Strength or your Dexterity, since the dagger has the finesse property.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Poisoned:</text>		<text>&#8226; A poisoned creature has disadvantage on attack rolls and ability checks.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 161</text>		<modifier category="bonus">weapon attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">weapon damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d4</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L,T</property>		<range>20/60</range>		<roll>2d10</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dancing Greatsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You can use a bonus action to toss this magic sword into the air and speak the command word. When you do so, the sword begins to hover, flies up to 30 feet, and attacks one creature of your choice within 5 feet of it. The sword uses your attack roll and ability score modifier to damage rolls.</text>		<text>While the sword hovers, you can use a bonus action to cause it to fly up to 30 feet to another spot within 30 feet of you. As part of the same bonus action, you can cause the sword to attack one creature within 5 feet of it.</text>		<text>After the hovering sword attacks for the fourth time, it flies up to 30 feet and tries to return to your hand. If you have no hand free, it falls to the ground at your feet. If the sword has no unobstructed path to you, it moves as close to you as it can and then falls to the ground. It also ceases to hover if you grasp it or move more than 30 feet away from it.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 161</text>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dancing Longsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You can use a bonus action to toss this magic sword into the air and speak the command word. When you do so, the sword begins to hover, flies up to 30 feet, and attacks one creature of your choice within 5 feet of it. The sword uses your attack roll and ability score modifier to damage rolls.</text>		<text>While the sword hovers, you can use a bonus action to cause it to fly up to 30 feet to another spot within 30 feet of you. As part of the same bonus action, you can cause the sword to attack one creature within 5 feet of it.</text>		<text>After the hovering sword attacks for the fourth time, it flies up to 30 feet and tries to return to your hand. If you have no hand free, it falls to the ground at your feet. If the sword has no unobstructed path to you, it moves as close to you as it can and then falls to the ground. It also ceases to hover if you grasp it or move more than 30 feet away from it.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 161</text>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dancing Rapier</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You can use a bonus action to toss this magic sword into the air and speak the command word. When you do so, the sword begins to hover, flies up to 30 feet, and attacks one creature of your choice within 5 feet of it. The sword uses your attack roll and ability score modifier to damage rolls.</text>		<text>While the sword hovers, you can use a bonus action to cause it to fly up to 30 feet to another spot within 30 feet of you. As part of the same bonus action, you can cause the sword to attack one creature within 5 feet of it.</text>		<text>After the hovering sword attacks for the fourth time, it flies up to 30 feet and tries to return to your hand. If you have no hand free, it falls to the ground at your feet. If the sword has no unobstructed path to you, it moves as close to you as it can and then falls to the ground. It also ceases to hover if you grasp it or move more than 30 feet away from it.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 161</text>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dancing Scimitar</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You can use a bonus action to toss this magic sword into the air and speak the command word. When you do so, the sword begins to hover, flies up to 30 feet, and attacks one creature of your choice within 5 feet of it. The sword uses your attack roll and ability score modifier to damage rolls.</text>		<text>While the sword hovers, you can use a bonus action to cause it to fly up to 30 feet to another spot within 30 feet of you. As part of the same bonus action, you can cause the sword to attack one creature within 5 feet of it.</text>		<text>After the hovering sword attacks for the fourth time, it flies up to 30 feet and tries to return to your hand. If you have no hand free, it falls to the ground at your feet. If the sword has no unobstructed path to you, it moves as close to you as it can and then falls to the ground. It also ceases to hover if you grasp it or move more than 30 feet away from it.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 161</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dancing Shortsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You can use a bonus action to toss this magic sword into the air and speak the command word. When you do so, the sword begins to hover, flies up to 30 feet, and attacks one creature of your choice within 5 feet of it. The sword uses your attack roll and ability score modifier to damage rolls.</text>		<text>While the sword hovers, you can use a bonus action to cause it to fly up to 30 feet to another spot within 30 feet of you. As part of the same bonus action, you can cause the sword to attack one creature within 5 feet of it.</text>		<text>After the hovering sword attacks for the fourth time, it flies up to 30 feet and tries to return to your hand. If you have no hand free, it falls to the ground at your feet. If the sword has no unobstructed path to you, it moves as close to you as it can and then falls to the ground. It also ceases to hover if you grasp it or move more than 30 feet away from it.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 161</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Defender Greatsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>The first time you attack with the sword on each of your turns, you can transfer some or all of the sword's bonus to your Armor Class, instead of using the bonus on any attacks that turn. For example, you could reduce the bonus to your attack and damage rolls to +1 and gain a +2 bonus to AC. The adjusted bonuses remain in effect until the start of your next turn, although you must hold the sword to gain a bonus to AC from it.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 164</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Defender Longsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>The first time you attack with the sword on each of your turns, you can transfer some or all of the sword's bonus to your Armor Class, instead of using the bonus on any attacks that turn. For example, you could reduce the bonus to your attack and damage rolls to +1 and gain a +2 bonus to AC. The adjusted bonuses remain in effect until the start of your next turn, although you must hold the sword to gain a bonus to AC from it.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 164</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Defender Rapier</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>The first time you attack with the sword on each of your turns, you can transfer some or all of the sword's bonus to your Armor Class, instead of using the bonus on any attacks that turn. For example, you could reduce the bonus to your attack and damage rolls to +1 and gain a +2 bonus to AC. The adjusted bonuses remain in effect until the start of your next turn, although you must hold the sword to gain a bonus to AC from it.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 164</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Defender Scimitar</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>The first time you attack with the sword on each of your turns, you can transfer some or all of the sword's bonus to your Armor Class, instead of using the bonus on any attacks that turn. For example, you could reduce the bonus to your attack and damage rolls to +1 and gain a +2 bonus to AC. The adjusted bonuses remain in effect until the start of your next turn, although you must hold the sword to gain a bonus to AC from it.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 164</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Defender Shortsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>The first time you attack with the sword on each of your turns, you can transfer some or all of the sword's bonus to your Armor Class, instead of using the bonus on any attacks that turn. For example, you could reduce the bonus to your attack and damage rolls to +1 and gain a +2 bonus to AC. The adjusted bonuses remain in effect until the start of your next turn, although you must hold the sword to gain a bonus to AC from it.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 164</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dragon Slayer Greatsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a dragon with this weapon, the dragon takes an extra 3d6 damage of the weapon's type. For the purpose of this weapon, "dragon" refers to any creature with the dragon type, including dragon turtles and wyverns.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 166</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>		<roll>3d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dragon Slayer Longsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a dragon with this weapon, the dragon takes an extra 3d6 damage of the weapon's type. For the purpose of this weapon, "dragon" refers to any creature with the dragon type, including dragon turtles and wyverns.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 166</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>		<roll>3d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dragon Slayer Rapier</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a dragon with this weapon, the dragon takes an extra 3d6 damage of the weapon's type. For the purpose of this weapon, "dragon" refers to any creature with the dragon type, including dragon turtles and wyverns.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 166</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F</property>		<range></range>		<roll>3d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dragon Slayer Scimitar</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a dragon with this weapon, the dragon takes an extra 3d6 damage of the weapon's type. For the purpose of this weapon, "dragon" refers to any creature with the dragon type, including dragon turtles and wyverns.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 166</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>3d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dragon Slayer Shortsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a dragon with this weapon, the dragon takes an extra 3d6 damage of the weapon's type. For the purpose of this weapon, "dragon" refers to any creature with the dragon type, including dragon turtles and wyverns.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 166</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>3d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Dwarven Thrower</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Dwarf</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. It has the thrown property with a normal range of 20 feet and a long range of 60 feet. When you hit with a ranged attack using this weapon, it deals an extra 1d8 damage or, if the target is a giant, 2d8 damage. Immediately after the attack, the weapon flies back to your hand.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Range: A weapon that can be used to make a ranged attack has a range shown in parentheses after the ammunition or thrown property. The range lists two numbers. The first is the weapon's normal range in feet, and the second indicates the weapon's maximum range. When attacking a target beyond normal range, you have disadvantage on the attack roll. You can't attack a target beyond the weapon's long range.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Thrown: If a weapon has the thrown property, you can throw the weapon to make a ranged attack. If the weapon is a melee weapon, you use the same ability modifier for that attack roll and damage roll that you would use for a melee attack with the weapon. For example, if you throw a handaxe, you use your Strength, but if you throw a dagger, you can use either your Strength or your Dexterity, since the dagger has the finesse property.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 167</text>		<modifier category="bonus">weapon attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">weapon damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>B</dmgType>		<property>T,V</property>		<range>20/60</range>		<roll>1d8</roll>		<roll>2d8</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Flame Tongue Greatsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You can use a bonus action to speak this magic sword' command word, causing flames to erupt from the blade. These flames shed bright light in a 40-foot radius and dim light for an additional 40 feet. While the sword is ablaze, it deals an extra 2d6 fire damage to any target it hits. The flames last until you use a bonus action to speak the command word again or until you drop or sheathe the sword.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 170</text>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Flame Tongue Longsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You can use a bonus action to speak this magic sword' command word, causing flames to erupt from the blade. These flames shed bright light in a 40-foot radius and dim light for an additional 40 feet. While the sword is ablaze, it deals an extra 2d6 fire damage to any target it hits. The flames last until you use a bonus action to speak the command word again or until you drop or sheathe the sword.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 170</text>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Flame Tongue Rapier</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You can use a bonus action to speak this magic sword' command word, causing flames to erupt from the blade. These flames shed bright light in a 40-foot radius and dim light for an additional 40 feet. While the sword is ablaze, it deals an extra 2d6 fire damage to any target it hits. The flames last until you use a bonus action to speak the command word again or until you drop or sheathe the sword.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 170</text>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Flame Tongue Scimitar</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You can use a bonus action to speak this magic sword' command word, causing flames to erupt from the blade. These flames shed bright light in a 40-foot radius and dim light for an additional 40 feet. While the sword is ablaze, it deals an extra 2d6 fire damage to any target it hits. The flames last until you use a bonus action to speak the command word again or until you drop or sheathe the sword.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 170</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Flame Tongue Shortsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You can use a bonus action to speak this magic sword' command word, causing flames to erupt from the blade. These flames shed bright light in a 40-foot radius and dim light for an additional 40 feet. While the sword is ablaze, it deals an extra 2d6 fire damage to any target it hits. The flames last until you use a bonus action to speak the command word again or until you drop or sheathe the sword.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 170</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Frost Brand Greatsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you hit with an attack using this magic sword, the target takes an extra 1d6 cold damage. In addition, while you hold the sword, you have resistance to fire damage.</text>		<text>In freezing temperatures, the blade sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet.</text>		<text>When you draw this weapon, you can extinguish all nonmagical flames within 30 feet of you. This property can be used no more than once per hour.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 171</text>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Frost Brand Longsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you hit with an attack using this magic sword, the target takes an extra 1d6 cold damage. In addition, while you hold the sword, you have resistance to fire damage.</text>		<text>In freezing temperatures, the blade sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet.</text>		<text>When you draw this weapon, you can extinguish all nonmagical flames within 30 feet of you. This property can be used no more than once per hour.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 171</text>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Frost Brand Rapier</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you hit with an attack using this magic sword, the target takes an extra 1d6 cold damage. In addition, while you hold the sword, you have resistance to fire damage.</text>		<text>In freezing temperatures, the blade sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet.</text>		<text>When you draw this weapon, you can extinguish all nonmagical flames within 30 feet of you. This property can be used no more than once per hour.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 171</text>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F</property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Frost Brand Scimitar</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you hit with an attack using this magic sword, the target takes an extra 1d6 cold damage. In addition, while you hold the sword, you have resistance to fire damage.</text>		<text>In freezing temperatures, the blade sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet.</text>		<text>When you draw this weapon, you can extinguish all nonmagical flames within 30 feet of you. This property can be used no more than once per hour.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 171</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Frost Brand Shortsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you hit with an attack using this magic sword, the target takes an extra 1d6 cold damage. In addition, while you hold the sword, you have resistance to fire damage.</text>		<text>In freezing temperatures, the blade sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet.</text>		<text>When you draw this weapon, you can extinguish all nonmagical flames within 30 feet of you. This property can be used no more than once per hour.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 171</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Giant Slayer Battleaxe</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>4</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a giant with it, the giant takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, "giant" refers to any creature with the giant type, including ettins and trolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Prone:</text>		<text>&#8226; A prone creature's only movement option is to crawl, unless it stands up and thereby ends the condition.</text>		<text>&#8226; The creature has disadvantage on attack rolls.</text>		<text>&#8226; An attack roll against the creature has advantage if the attacker is within 5 feet of the creature. Otherwise, the attack roll has disadvantage.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 172</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Giant Slayer Greataxe</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>7</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a giant with it, the giant takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, "giant" refers to any creature with the giant type, including ettins and trolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Prone:</text>		<text>&#8226; A prone creature's only movement option is to crawl, unless it stands up and thereby ends the condition.</text>		<text>&#8226; The creature has disadvantage on attack rolls.</text>		<text>&#8226; An attack roll against the creature has advantage if the attacker is within 5 feet of the creature. Otherwise, the attack roll has disadvantage.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 172</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d12</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Giant Slayer Greatsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a giant with it, the giant takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, "giant" refers to any creature with the giant type, including ettins and trolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Prone:</text>		<text>&#8226; A prone creature's only movement option is to crawl, unless it stands up and thereby ends the condition.</text>		<text>&#8226; The creature has disadvantage on attack rolls.</text>		<text>&#8226; An attack roll against the creature has advantage if the attacker is within 5 feet of the creature. Otherwise, the attack roll has disadvantage.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 172</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Giant Slayer Handaxe</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a giant with it, the giant takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, "giant" refers to any creature with the giant type, including ettins and trolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Range: A weapon that can be used to make a ranged attack has a range shown in parentheses after the ammunition or thrown property. The range lists two numbers. The first is the weapon's normal range in feet, and the second indicates the weapon's maximum range. When attacking a target beyond normal range, you have disadvantage on the attack roll. You can't attack a target beyond the weapon's long range.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Thrown: If a weapon has the thrown property, you can throw the weapon to make a ranged attack. If the weapon is a melee weapon, you use the same ability modifier for that attack roll and damage roll that you would use for a melee attack with the weapon. For example, if you throw a handaxe, you use your Strength, but if you throw a dagger, you can use either your Strength or your Dexterity, since the dagger has the finesse property.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Prone:</text>		<text>&#8226; A prone creature's only movement option is to crawl, unless it stands up and thereby ends the condition.</text>		<text>&#8226; The creature has disadvantage on attack rolls.</text>		<text>&#8226; An attack roll against the creature has advantage if the attacker is within 5 feet of the creature. Otherwise, the attack roll has disadvantage.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 172</text>		<modifier category="bonus">weapon attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">weapon damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>L,T</property>		<range>20/60</range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Giant Slayer Longsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a giant with it, the giant takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, "giant" refers to any creature with the giant type, including ettins and trolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Prone:</text>		<text>&#8226; A prone creature's only movement option is to crawl, unless it stands up and thereby ends the condition.</text>		<text>&#8226; The creature has disadvantage on attack rolls.</text>		<text>&#8226; An attack roll against the creature has advantage if the attacker is within 5 feet of the creature. Otherwise, the attack roll has disadvantage.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 172</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Giant Slayer Rapier</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a giant with it, the giant takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, "giant" refers to any creature with the giant type, including ettins and trolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Prone:</text>		<text>&#8226; A prone creature's only movement option is to crawl, unless it stands up and thereby ends the condition.</text>		<text>&#8226; The creature has disadvantage on attack rolls.</text>		<text>&#8226; An attack roll against the creature has advantage if the attacker is within 5 feet of the creature. Otherwise, the attack roll has disadvantage.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 172</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Giant Slayer Scimitar</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a giant with it, the giant takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, "giant" refers to any creature with the giant type, including ettins and trolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Prone:</text>		<text>&#8226; A prone creature's only movement option is to crawl, unless it stands up and thereby ends the condition.</text>		<text>&#8226; The creature has disadvantage on attack rolls.</text>		<text>&#8226; An attack roll against the creature has advantage if the attacker is within 5 feet of the creature. Otherwise, the attack roll has disadvantage.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 172</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Giant Slayer Shortsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>When you hit a giant with it, the giant takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, "giant" refers to any creature with the giant type, including ettins and trolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Prone:</text>		<text>&#8226; A prone creature's only movement option is to crawl, unless it stands up and thereby ends the condition.</text>		<text>&#8226; The creature has disadvantage on attack rolls.</text>		<text>&#8226; An attack roll against the creature has advantage if the attacker is within 5 feet of the creature. Otherwise, the attack roll has disadvantage.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 172</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Greatsword of Life Stealing</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you attack a creature with this magic weapon and roll a 20 on the attack roll, that target takes an extra 10 necrotic damage if it isn't a construct or an undead. You also gain 10 temporary hit points.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Greatsword of Sharpness</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you attack an object with this magic sword and hit, maximize your weapon damage dice against the target.</text>		<text>When you attack a creature with this weapon and roll a 20 on the attack roll, that target takes an extra 14 slashing damage. Then roll another d20. If you roll a 20, you lop off one of the target's limbs, with the effect of such loss determined by the DM. If the creature has no limb to sever, you lop off a portion of its body instead.</text>		<text>In addition, you can speak the sword's command to cause the blade to shed bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet. Speaking the command word again or sheathing the sword puts out the light.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Greatsword of Vengeance</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: This sword is cursed and possessed by a vengeful spirit. Becoming attuned to it extends the curse to you. As long as you remain cursed, you are unwilling to part with the sword, keeping it on your person at all times. While attuned to this weapon, you have disadvantage on attack rolls made with weapons other than this one.</text>		<text>In addition, while the sword is on your person, you must succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw whenever you take damage in combat. On a failed save you must attack the creature that damaged you until you drop to 0 hit points or it does, or until you can't reach the creature to make a melee attack against it.</text>		<text>You can break the curse in the usual ways. Alternatively, casting banishment on the sword forces the vengeful spirit to leave it. The sword then becomes a +1 weapon with no other properties.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Greatsword of Wounding</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	Hit points lost to this weapon's damage can be regained only through a short or long rest, rather than by regeneration, magic, or any other means.</text>		<text>Once per turn, when you hit a creature with an attack using this magic weapon, you can wound the target. At the start of each of the wounded creature's turns, it takes 1d4 necrotic damage for each time you've wounded it, and it can then make a DC 15 Constitution saving throw, ending the effect of all such wounds on itself on a success. Alternatively, the wounded creature, or a creature within 5 feet of it, can use an action to make a DC 15 Wisdom (Medicine) check, ending the effect of such wounds on it on a success.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 207</text>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d4</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Hammer of Thunderbolts</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>10</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Giant's Bane (Requires Attunement):</text>		<text>You must be wearing a belt of giant strength (any variety) and gauntlets of ogre power to attune to this weapon. The attunement ends if you take off either of those items. While you are attuned to this weapon and holding it, your Strength score increases by 4 and can exceed 20, but not 30. When you roll a 20 on an attack roll made with this weapon against a giant, the giant must succeed on a DC 17 Constitution saving throw or die.</text>		<text>The hammer also has 5 charges. While attuned to it, you can expend 1 charge and make a ranged weapon attack with the hammer, hurling it as if it had the thrown property with a normal range of 20 feet and a long range of 60 feet. If the attack hits, the hammer unleashes a thunderclap audible out to 300 feet. The target and every creature within 30 feet of it must succeed on a DC 17 Constitution saving throw or be stunned until the end of your next turn. The hammer regains 1d4+1 expended charges daily at dawn.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Stunned:</text>		<text>&#8226; A stunned creature is incapacitated, meaning it can't take actions or reactions, can't move, and can speak only falteringly.</text>		<text>&#8226; The creature automatically fails Strength and Dexterity saving throws.</text>		<text>&#8226; Attack rolls against the creature have advantage.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 173</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2>2d6</dmg2>		<dmgType>B</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d4+1</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Holy Avenger Greatsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Paladin</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. When you hit a fiend or an undead with it, that creature takes an extra 2d10 radiant damage.</text>		<text>While you hold the drawn sword, it creates an aura in a 10-foot radius around you. You and all creatures friendly to you in the aura have advantage on saving throws against spells and other magical effects. If you have 17 or more levels in the paladin class, the radius of the aura increases to 30 feet.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 174</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d10</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Holy Avenger Longsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Paladin</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. When you hit a fiend or an undead with it, that creature takes an extra 2d10 radiant damage.</text>		<text>While you hold the drawn sword, it creates an aura in a 10-foot radius around you. You and all creatures friendly to you in the aura have advantage on saving throws against spells and other magical effects. If you have 17 or more levels in the paladin class, the radius of the aura increases to 30 feet.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 174</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d10</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Holy Avenger Rapier</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Paladin</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. When you hit a fiend or an undead with it, that creature takes an extra 2d10 radiant damage.</text>		<text>While you hold the drawn sword, it creates an aura in a 10-foot radius around you. You and all creatures friendly to you in the aura have advantage on saving throws against spells and other magical effects. If you have 17 or more levels in the paladin class, the radius of the aura increases to 30 feet.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 174</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d10</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Holy Avenger Scimitar</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Paladin</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. When you hit a fiend or an undead with it, that creature takes an extra 2d10 radiant damage.</text>		<text>While you hold the drawn sword, it creates an aura in a 10-foot radius around you. You and all creatures friendly to you in the aura have advantage on saving throws against spells and other magical effects. If you have 17 or more levels in the paladin class, the radius of the aura increases to 30 feet.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 174</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d10</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Holy Avenger Shortsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Paladin</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. When you hit a fiend or an undead with it, that creature takes an extra 2d10 radiant damage.</text>		<text>While you hold the drawn sword, it creates an aura in a 10-foot radius around you. You and all creatures friendly to you in the aura have advantage on saving throws against spells and other magical effects. If you have 17 or more levels in the paladin class, the radius of the aura increases to 30 feet.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 174</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d10</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Javelin of Lightning</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>	This javelin is a magic weapon. When you hurl it and speak its command word, it transforms into a bolt of lightning, forming a line 5 feet wide that extends out from you to a target within 120 feet. Each creature in the line excluding you and the target must make a DC 13 Dexterity saving throw, taking 4d6 lightning damage on a failed save, and half as much damage on a successful one. The lightning bolt turns back into a javelin when it reaches the target. Make a ranged weapon attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes damage from the javelin plus 4d6 lightning damage.</text>		<text>The javelin's property can't be used again until the next dawn. In the meantime, the javelin can still be used as a magic weapon.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Range: A weapon that can be used to make a ranged attack has a range shown in parentheses after the ammunition or thrown property. The range lists two numbers. The first is the weapon's normal range in feet, and the second indicates the weapon's maximum range. When attacking a target beyond normal range, you have disadvantage on the attack roll. You can't attack a target beyond the weapon's long range.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Thrown: If a weapon has the thrown property, you can throw the weapon to make a ranged attack. If the weapon is a melee weapon, you use the same ability modifier for that attack roll and damage roll that you would use for a melee attack with the weapon. For example, if you throw a handaxe, you use your Strength, but if you throw a dagger, you can use either your Strength or your Dexterity, since the dagger has the finesse property.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 178</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>T</property>		<range>30/120</range>		<roll>4d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Longsword of Life Stealing</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you attack a creature with this magic weapon and roll a 20 on the attack roll, that target takes an extra 10 necrotic damage if it isn't a construct or an undead. You also gain 10 temporary hit points.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Longsword of Sharpness</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you attack an object with this magic sword and hit, maximize your weapon damage dice against the target.</text>		<text>When you attack a creature with this weapon and roll a 20 on the attack roll, that target takes an extra 14 slashing damage. Then roll another d20. If you roll a 20, you lop off one of the target's limbs, with the effect of such loss determined by the DM. If the creature has no limb to sever, you lop off a portion of its body instead.</text>		<text>In addition, you can speak the sword's command to cause the blade to shed bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet. Speaking the command word again or sheathing the sword puts out the light.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Longsword of Vengeance</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: This sword is cursed and possessed by a vengeful spirit. Becoming attuned to it extends the curse to you. As long as you remain cursed, you are unwilling to part with the sword, keeping it on your person at all times. While attuned to this weapon, you have disadvantage on attack rolls made with weapons other than this one.</text>		<text>In addition, while the sword is on your person, you must succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw whenever you take damage in combat. On a failed save you must attack the creature that damaged you until you drop to 0 hit points or it does, or until you can't reach the creature to make a melee attack against it.</text>		<text>You can break the curse in the usual ways. Alternatively, casting banishment on the sword forces the vengeful spirit to leave it. The sword then becomes a +1 weapon with no other properties.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Longsword of Wounding</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	Hit points lost to this weapon's damage can be regained only through a short or long rest, rather than by regeneration, magic, or any other means.</text>		<text>Once per turn, when you hit a creature with an attack using this magic weapon, you can wound the target. At the start of each of the wounded creature's turns, it takes 1d4 necrotic damage for each time you've wounded it, and it can then make a DC 15 Constitution saving throw, ending the effect of all such wounds on itself on a success. Alternatively, the wounded creature, or a creature within 5 feet of it, can use an action to make a DC 15 Wisdom (Medicine) check, ending the effect of such wounds on it on a success.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 207</text>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d4</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Luck Blade Greatsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. While the sword is on your person, you also gain a +1 bonus to saving throws.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Luck: If the sword is on your person, you can call on its luck (no action required) to reroll one attack roll, ability check, or saving throw you dislike. You must use the second roll. This property can't be used again until the next dawn.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Wish: The sword has 1d4-1 charges. While holding it, you can use an action to expend 1 charge and cast the wish spell from it. This property can't be used again until the next dawn. The sword loses this property if it has no charges.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 179</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">saving throws +1</modifier>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Luck Blade Longsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. While the sword is on your person, you also gain a +1 bonus to saving throws.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Luck: If the sword is on your person, you can call on its luck (no action required) to reroll one attack roll, ability check, or saving throw you dislike. You must use the second roll. This property can't be used again until the next dawn.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Wish: The sword has 1d4-1 charges. While holding it, you can use an action to expend 1 charge and cast the wish spell from it. This property can't be used again until the next dawn. The sword loses this property if it has no charges.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 179</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">saving throws +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Luck Blade Rapier</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. While the sword is on your person, you also gain a +1 bonus to saving throws.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Luck: If the sword is on your person, you can call on its luck (no action required) to reroll one attack roll, ability check, or saving throw you dislike. You must use the second roll. This property can't be used again until the next dawn.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Wish: The sword has 1d4-1 charges. While holding it, you can use an action to expend 1 charge and cast the wish spell from it. This property can't be used again until the next dawn. The sword loses this property if it has no charges.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 179</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">saving throws +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Luck Blade Scimitar</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. While the sword is on your person, you also gain a +1 bonus to saving throws.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Luck: If the sword is on your person, you can call on its luck (no action required) to reroll one attack roll, ability check, or saving throw you dislike. You must use the second roll. This property can't be used again until the next dawn.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Wish: The sword has 1d4-1 charges. While holding it, you can use an action to expend 1 charge and cast the wish spell from it. This property can't be used again until the next dawn. The sword loses this property if it has no charges.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 179</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">saving throws +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Luck Blade Shortsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. While the sword is on your person, you also gain a +1 bonus to saving throws.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Luck: If the sword is on your person, you can call on its luck (no action required) to reroll one attack roll, ability check, or saving throw you dislike. You must use the second roll. This property can't be used again until the next dawn.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Wish: The sword has 1d4-1 charges. While holding it, you can use an action to expend 1 charge and cast the wish spell from it. This property can't be used again until the next dawn. The sword loses this property if it has no charges.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 179</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">saving throws +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Mace of Disruption</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>4</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you hit a fiend or an undead with this magic weapon, that creature takes an extra 2d6 radiant damage. If the target has 25 hit points or fewer after taking this damage, it must succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw or be destroyed. On a successful save, the creature becomes frightened of you until the end of your next turn.</text>		<text>While you hold this weapon, it sheds bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Frightened:</text>		<text>&#8226; A frightened creature has disadvantage on ability checks and attack rolls while the source of its fear is within line of sight.</text>		<text>&#8226; The creature can't willingly move closer to the source of its fear.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 179</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>B</dmgType>		<property></property>		<range></range>		<roll>2d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Mace of Smiting</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>4</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. The bonus increases to +3 when you use the mace to attack a construct.</text>		<text>When you roll a 20 on an attack roll made with this weapon, the target takes an extra 7 bludgeoning damage, or an extra 14 bludgeoning damage if it's a construct. If a construct has 25 hit points or fewer after taking this damage, it is destroyed.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 179</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>B</dmgType>		<property></property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Mace of Terror</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>4</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	This magic weapon has 3 charges. While holding it, you can use an action and expend 1 charge to release a wave of terror. Each creature of your choice in a 30-foot radius extending from you must succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw or become frightened of you for 1 minute. While it is frightened in this way, a creature must spend its turns trying to move as far away from you as it can, and it can't willingly move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can't take reactions. For its action it can use only the Dash action or try to escape from an effect that prevents it from moving. If it has nowhere it can move, the creature can use the Dodge action. At the end of each of its turns, a creature can repeat the saving throw, ending the effect on itself on a success.</text>		<text>The mace regains 1d3 expended charges daily at dawn.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Frightened:</text>		<text>&#8226; A frightened creature has disadvantage on ability checks and attack rolls while the source of its fear is within line of sight.</text>		<text>&#8226; The creature can't willingly move closer to the source of its fear.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 180</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>B</dmgType>		<property></property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d3</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Nine Lives Stealer Greatsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>The sword has 1d8+1 charges. If you score a critical hit against a creature that has fewer than 100 hit points, it must succeed on a DC 15 Constitution saving throw or be slain instantly as the sword tears its life force from its body (a construct or an undead is immune). The sword loses 1 charge if the creature is slain. When the sword has no charges remaining, it loses this property.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 183</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +2</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +2</modifier>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Nine Lives Stealer Longsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>The sword has 1d8+1 charges. If you score a critical hit against a creature that has fewer than 100 hit points, it must succeed on a DC 15 Constitution saving throw or be slain instantly as the sword tears its life force from its body (a construct or an undead is immune). The sword loses 1 charge if the creature is slain. When the sword has no charges remaining, it loses this property.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 183</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +2</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +2</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Nine Lives Stealer Rapier</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>The sword has 1d8+1 charges. If you score a critical hit against a creature that has fewer than 100 hit points, it must succeed on a DC 15 Constitution saving throw or be slain instantly as the sword tears its life force from its body (a construct or an undead is immune). The sword loses 1 charge if the creature is slain. When the sword has no charges remaining, it loses this property.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 183</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +2</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +2</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Nine Lives Stealer Scimitar</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>The sword has 1d8+1 charges. If you score a critical hit against a creature that has fewer than 100 hit points, it must succeed on a DC 15 Constitution saving throw or be slain instantly as the sword tears its life force from its body (a construct or an undead is immune). The sword loses 1 charge if the creature is slain. When the sword has no charges remaining, it loses this property.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 183</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +2</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +2</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Nine Lives Stealer Shortsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text>The sword has 1d8+1 charges. If you score a critical hit against a creature that has fewer than 100 hit points, it must succeed on a DC 15 Constitution saving throw or be slain instantly as the sword tears its life force from its body (a construct or an undead is immune). The sword loses 1 charge if the creature is slain. When the sword has no charges remaining, it loses this property.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 183</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +2</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +2</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Rapier of Life Stealing</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you attack a creature with this magic weapon and roll a 20 on the attack roll, that target takes an extra 10 necrotic damage if it isn't a construct or an undead. You also gain 10 temporary hit points.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Rapier of Vengeance</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: This sword is cursed and possessed by a vengeful spirit. Becoming attuned to it extends the curse to you. As long as you remain cursed, you are unwilling to part with the sword, keeping it on your person at all times. While attuned to this weapon, you have disadvantage on attack rolls made with weapons other than this one.</text>		<text>In addition, while the sword is on your person, you must succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw whenever you take damage in combat. On a failed save you must attack the creature that damaged you until you drop to 0 hit points or it does, or until you can't reach the creature to make a melee attack against it.</text>		<text>You can break the curse in the usual ways. Alternatively, casting banishment on the sword forces the vengeful spirit to leave it. The sword then becomes a +1 weapon with no other properties.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Rapier of Wounding</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	Hit points lost to this weapon's damage can be regained only through a short or long rest, rather than by regeneration, magic, or any other means.</text>		<text>Once per turn, when you hit a creature with an attack using this magic weapon, you can wound the target. At the start of each of the wounded creature's turns, it takes 1d4 necrotic damage for each time you've wounded it, and it can then make a DC 15 Constitution saving throw, ending the effect of all such wounds on itself on a success. Alternatively, the wounded creature, or a creature within 5 feet of it, can use an action to make a DC 15 Wisdom (Medicine) check, ending the effect of such wounds on it on a success.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 207</text>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F</property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d4</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Scimitar of Life Stealing</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you attack a creature with this magic weapon and roll a 20 on the attack roll, that target takes an extra 10 necrotic damage if it isn't a construct or an undead. You also gain 10 temporary hit points.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Scimitar of Sharpness</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you attack an object with this magic sword and hit, maximize your weapon damage dice against the target.</text>		<text>When you attack a creature with this weapon and roll a 20 on the attack roll, that target takes an extra 14 slashing damage. Then roll another d20. If you roll a 20, you lop off one of the target's limbs, with the effect of such loss determined by the DM. If the creature has no limb to sever, you lop off a portion of its body instead.</text>		<text>In addition, you can speak the sword's command to cause the blade to shed bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet. Speaking the command word again or sheathing the sword puts out the light.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Scimitar of Speed</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. In addition, you can make one attack with it as a bonus action on each of your turns.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 199</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +2</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +2</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Scimitar of Vengeance</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: This sword is cursed and possessed by a vengeful spirit. Becoming attuned to it extends the curse to you. As long as you remain cursed, you are unwilling to part with the sword, keeping it on your person at all times. While attuned to this weapon, you have disadvantage on attack rolls made with weapons other than this one.</text>		<text>In addition, while the sword is on your person, you must succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw whenever you take damage in combat. On a failed save you must attack the creature that damaged you until you drop to 0 hit points or it does, or until you can't reach the creature to make a melee attack against it.</text>		<text>You can break the curse in the usual ways. Alternatively, casting banishment on the sword forces the vengeful spirit to leave it. The sword then becomes a +1 weapon with no other properties.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Scimitar of Wounding</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	Hit points lost to this weapon's damage can be regained only through a short or long rest, rather than by regeneration, magic, or any other means.</text>		<text>Once per turn, when you hit a creature with an attack using this magic weapon, you can wound the target. At the start of each of the wounded creature's turns, it takes 1d4 necrotic damage for each time you've wounded it, and it can then make a DC 15 Constitution saving throw, ending the effect of all such wounds on itself on a success. Alternatively, the wounded creature, or a creature within 5 feet of it, can use an action to make a DC 15 Wisdom (Medicine) check, ending the effect of such wounds on it on a success.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 207</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d4</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Shortsword of Life Stealing</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you attack a creature with this magic weapon and roll a 20 on the attack roll, that target takes an extra 10 necrotic damage if it isn't a construct or an undead. You also gain 10 temporary hit points.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Shortsword of Vengeance</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: This sword is cursed and possessed by a vengeful spirit. Becoming attuned to it extends the curse to you. As long as you remain cursed, you are unwilling to part with the sword, keeping it on your person at all times. While attuned to this weapon, you have disadvantage on attack rolls made with weapons other than this one.</text>		<text>In addition, while the sword is on your person, you must succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw whenever you take damage in combat. On a failed save you must attack the creature that damaged you until you drop to 0 hit points or it does, or until you can't reach the creature to make a melee attack against it.</text>		<text>You can break the curse in the usual ways. Alternatively, casting banishment on the sword forces the vengeful spirit to leave it. The sword then becomes a +1 weapon with no other properties.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +1</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +1</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Shortsword of Wounding</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	Hit points lost to this weapon's damage can be regained only through a short or long rest, rather than by regeneration, magic, or any other means.</text>		<text>Once per turn, when you hit a creature with an attack using this magic weapon, you can wound the target. At the start of each of the wounded creature's turns, it takes 1d4 necrotic damage for each time you've wounded it, and it can then make a DC 15 Constitution saving throw, ending the effect of all such wounds on itself on a success. Alternatively, the wounded creature, or a creature within 5 feet of it, can use an action to make a DC 15 Wisdom (Medicine) check, ending the effect of such wounds on it on a success.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 207</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d4</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Sun Blade</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>	This item appears to be a longsword hilt. While grasping the hilt, you can use a bonus action to cause a blade of pure radiance to spring into existence, or make the blade disappear. While the blade exists, this magic longsword has the finesse property. If you are proficient with shortswords or longswords, you are proficient with the sun blade.</text>		<text>You gain a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this weapon, which deals radiant damage instead of slashing damage. When you hit an undead with it, that target takes an extra 1d8 radiant damage.</text>		<text>The sword's luminous blade emits bright light in a 15-foot radius and dim light for an additional 15 feet. The light is sunlight. While the blade persists, you can use an action to expand or reduce its radius of bright and dim light by 5 feet each, to a maximum of 30 feet each or a minimum of 10 feet each.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 205</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +2</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +2</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,V</property>		<range></range>		<roll>1d8</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Sword of Answering (Answerer)</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Chaotic Good Creature)</text>		<text>	In the world of Greyhawk, only nine of these blades are known to exist. Each is patterned after the legendary sword Fragarach, which is variously translated as "Final Word." Each of the nine swords has its own name and alignment, and each bears a different gem in its pommel.</text>		<text>Answerer, the Chaotic Good sword, has an emerald set in its pommel.</text>		<text>You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this sword. In addition, while you hold the sword, you can use your reaction to make one melee attack with it against any creature in your reach that deals damage to you. You have advantage on the attack roll, and any damage dealt with this special attack ignores any damage immunity or resistance the target has.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Sword of Answering (Back Talker)</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Chaotic Evil Creature)</text>		<text>	In the world of Greyhawk, only nine of these blades are known to exist. Each is patterned after the legendary sword Fragarach, which is variously translated as "Final Word." Each of the nine swords has its own name and alignment, and each bears a different gem in its pommel.</text>		<text>Back Talker, the Chaotic Evil sword, has jet set in its pommel.</text>		<text>You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this sword. In addition, while you hold the sword, you can use your reaction to make one melee attack with it against any creature in your reach that deals damage to you. You have advantage on the attack roll, and any damage dealt with this special attack ignores any damage immunity or resistance the target has.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Sword of Answering (Concluder)</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Lawful Neutral Creature)</text>		<text>	In the world of Greyhawk, only nine of these blades are known to exist. Each is patterned after the legendary sword Fragarach, which is variously translated as "Final Word." Each of the nine swords has its own name and alignment, and each bears a different gem in its pommel.</text>		<text>Concluder, the Lawful Neutral sword, has an amethyst set in its pommel.</text>		<text>You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this sword. In addition, while you hold the sword, you can use your reaction to make one melee attack with it against any creature in your reach that deals damage to you. You have advantage on the attack roll, and any damage dealt with this special attack ignores any damage immunity or resistance the target has.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Sword of Answering (Last Quip)</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Chaotic Neutral Creature)</text>		<text>	In the world of Greyhawk, only nine of these blades are known to exist. Each is patterned after the legendary sword Fragarach, which is variously translated as "Final Word." Each of the nine swords has its own name and alignment, and each bears a different gem in its pommel.</text>		<text>Last Quip, the Chaotic Neutral sword, has a tourmaline set in its pommel.</text>		<text>You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this sword. In addition, while you hold the sword, you can use your reaction to make one melee attack with it against any creature in your reach that deals damage to you. You have advantage on the attack roll, and any damage dealt with this special attack ignores any damage immunity or resistance the target has.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Sword of Answering (Rebutter)</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Neutral Good Creature)</text>		<text>	In the world of Greyhawk, only nine of these blades are known to exist. Each is patterned after the legendary sword Fragarach, which is variously translated as "Final Word." Each of the nine swords has its own name and alignment, and each bears a different gem in its pommel.</text>		<text>Rebutter, the Neutral Good sword, has a  topaz set in its pommel.</text>		<text>You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this sword. In addition, while you hold the sword, you can use your reaction to make one melee attack with it against any creature in your reach that deals damage to you. You have advantage on the attack roll, and any damage dealt with this special attack ignores any damage immunity or resistance the target has.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Sword of Answering (Replier)</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Neutral Creature)</text>		<text>	In the world of Greyhawk, only nine of these blades are known to exist. Each is patterned after the legendary sword Fragarach, which is variously translated as "Final Word." Each of the nine swords has its own name and alignment, and each bears a different gem in its pommel.</text>		<text>Replier, the Neutral sword, has a peridot set in its pommel.</text>		<text>You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this sword. In addition, while you hold the sword, you can use your reaction to make one melee attack with it against any creature in your reach that deals damage to you. You have advantage on the attack roll, and any damage dealt with this special attack ignores any damage immunity or resistance the target has.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Sword of Answering (Retorter)</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Lawful Good Creature)</text>		<text>	In the world of Greyhawk, only nine of these blades are known to exist. Each is patterned after the legendary sword Fragarach, which is variously translated as "Final Word." Each of the nine swords has its own name and alignment, and each bears a different gem in its pommel.</text>		<text>Retorter, the Lawful Good sword, has an aquamarine set in its pommel.</text>		<text>You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this sword. In addition, while you hold the sword, you can use your reaction to make one melee attack with it against any creature in your reach that deals damage to you. You have advantage on the attack roll, and any damage dealt with this special attack ignores any damage immunity or resistance the target has.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Sword of Answering (Scather)</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Lawful Evil Creature)</text>		<text>	In the world of Greyhawk, only nine of these blades are known to exist. Each is patterned after the legendary sword Fragarach, which is variously translated as "Final Word." Each of the nine swords has its own name and alignment, and each bears a different gem in its pommel.</text>		<text>Scather, the Lawful Evil sword, has a  garnet set in its pommel.</text>		<text>You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this sword. In addition, while you hold the sword, you can use your reaction to make one melee attack with it against any creature in your reach that deals damage to you. You have advantage on the attack roll, and any damage dealt with this special attack ignores any damage immunity or resistance the target has.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Sword of Answering (Squelcher)</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement by a Neutral Evil Creature)</text>		<text>	In the world of Greyhawk, only nine of these blades are known to exist. Each is patterned after the legendary sword Fragarach, which is variously translated as "Final Word." Each of the nine swords has its own name and alignment, and each bears a different gem in its pommel.</text>		<text>Squelcher, the Neutral Evil sword, has a spinel set in its pommel.</text>		<text>You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this sword. In addition, while you hold the sword, you can use your reaction to make one melee attack with it against any creature in your reach that deals damage to you. You have advantage on the attack roll, and any damage dealt with this special attack ignores any damage immunity or resistance the target has.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 206</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Trident of Fish Command</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>4</weight>		<text>	This trident is a magic weapon. It has 3 charges. While you carry it, you can use an action and expend 1 charge to cast dominate beast (save DC 15) from it on a beast that has an innate swimming speed. The trident regains 1d3 expended charges daily at dawn.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Range: A weapon that can be used to make a ranged attack has a range shown in parentheses after the ammunition or thrown property. The range lists two numbers. The first is the weapon's normal range in feet, and the second indicates the weapon's maximum range. When attacking a target beyond normal range, you have disadvantage on the attack roll. You can't attack a target beyond the weapon's long range.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Thrown: If a weapon has the thrown property, you can throw the weapon to make a ranged attack. If the weapon is a melee weapon, you use the same ability modifier for that attack roll and damage roll that you would use for a melee attack with the weapon. For example, if you throw a handaxe, you use your Strength, but if you throw a dagger, you can use either your Strength or your Dexterity, since the dagger has the finesse property.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 209</text>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d8</dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>T,V</property>		<range>20/60</range>		<roll>1d3</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Vorpal Greatsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. In addition, the weapon ignores resistance to slashing damage.</text>		<text>When you attack a creature that has at least one head with this weapon and roll a 20 on the attack roll, you cut off one of the creature's heads. The creature dies if it can't survive without the lost head. A creature is immune to this effect if it is immune to slashing damage, doesn't have or need a head, has legendary actions, or the DM decides that the creature is too big for its head to be cut off with this weapon. Such a creature instead takes an extra 6d8 slashing damage from the hit.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 209</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>2d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>H,2H</property>		<range></range>		<roll>6d8</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Vorpal Longsword</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. In addition, the weapon ignores resistance to slashing damage.</text>		<text>When you attack a creature that has at least one head with this weapon and roll a 20 on the attack roll, you cut off one of the creature's heads. The creature dies if it can't survive without the lost head. A creature is immune to this effect if it is immune to slashing damage, doesn't have or need a head, has legendary actions, or the DM decides that the creature is too big for its head to be cut off with this weapon. Such a creature instead takes an extra 6d8 slashing damage from the hit.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Versatile: This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property &#8212; the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 209</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2>1d10</dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>V</property>		<range></range>		<roll>6d8</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Vorpal Scimitar</name>		<type>M</type>		<weight>3</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. In addition, the weapon ignores resistance to slashing damage.</text>		<text>When you attack a creature that has at least one head with this weapon and roll a 20 on the attack roll, you cut off one of the creature's heads. The creature dies if it can't survive without the lost head. A creature is immune to this effect if it is immune to slashing damage, doesn't have or need a head, has legendary actions, or the DM decides that the creature is too big for its head to be cut off with this weapon. Such a creature instead takes an extra 6d8 slashing damage from the hit.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Finesse: When making an attack with a finesse weapon, you use your choice of your Strength or Dexterity modifier for the attack and damage rolls. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Light: A light weapon is small and easy to handle, making it ideal for use when fighting with two weapons.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 209</text>		<modifier category="bonus">melee attacks +3</modifier>		<modifier category="bonus">melee damage +3</modifier>		<dmg1>1d6</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>S</dmgType>		<property>F,L</property>		<range></range>		<roll>6d8</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Elven Chain</name>		<type>MA</type>		<weight>20</weight>		<text>	You gain a +1 bonus to AC while you wear this armor. You are considered proficient with this armor even if you lack proficiency with medium armor.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 209</text>		<modifier category="bonus">ac +1</modifier>		<ac>13</ac>		<strength></strength>		<stealth></stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Oathbow</name>		<type>R</type>		<weight>2</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	When you nock an arrow on this bow, it whispers in Elvish, "Swift defeat to my enemies." When you use this weapon to make a ranged attack, you can, as a command phrase, say, "Swift death to you who have wronged me." The target of your attack becomes your sworn enemy until it dies or until dawn seven days later. You can have only one such sworn enemy at a time. When your sworn enemy dies, you can choose a new one after the next dawn.</text>		<text>When you make a ranged attack roll with this weapon against your sworn enemy, you have advantage on the roll. In addition, your target gains no benefit from cover, other than total cover, and you suffer no disadvantage due to long range. If the attack hits, your sworn enemy takes an extra 3d6 piercing damage.</text>		<text>While your sworn enemy lives, you have disadvantage on attack rolls with all other weapons.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Ammunition: You can use a weapon that has the ammunition property to make a ranged attack only if you have ammunition to fire from the weapon. Each time you attack with the weapon, you expend one piece of ammunition. Drawing the ammunition from a quiver, case, or other container is part of the attack. Loading a one-handed weapon requires a free hand. At the end of the battle, you can recover half your expended ammunition by taking a minute to search the battlefield.</text>		<text>If you use a weapon that has the ammunition property to make a melee attack, you treat the weapon as an improvised weapon. A sling must be loaded to deal any damage when used in this way.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Heavy: Small creatures have disadvantage on attack rolls with heavy weapons. A heavy weapon's size and bulk make it too large for a Small creature to use effectively.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Range: A weapon that can be used to make a ranged attack has a range shown in parentheses after the ammunition or thrown property. The range lists two numbers. The first is the weapon's normal range in feet, and the second indicates the weapon's maximum range. When attacking a target beyond normal range, you have disadvantage on the attack roll. You can't attack a target beyond the weapon's long range.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Two-Handed: This weapon requires two hands to use.  When not attacking, you may hold the weapon in one hand.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 168</text>		<dmg1>1d8</dmg1>		<dmg2></dmg2>		<dmgType>P</dmgType>		<property>A,H,2H</property>		<range>150/600</range>		<roll>3d6</roll>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Animated Shield</name>		<type>S</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	While holding this shield, you can speak its command word as a bonus action to cause it to animate. The shield leaps into the air and hovers in your space to protect you as if you were wielding it, leaving your hands free. The shield remains animated for 1 minute, until you use a bonus action to end this effect, or until you are incapacitated or die, at which point the shield falls to the ground or into your hand if you have one free.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 183</text>		<ac>2</ac>		<strength></strength>		<stealth></stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Arrow-Catching Shield</name>		<type>S</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	You gain a +2 bonus to AC against ranged attacks while you wield this shield. This bonus is in addition to the shield's normal bonus to AC. In addition, whenever an attacker makes a ranged attack against a target within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to become the target of the attack instead.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 152</text>		<ac>2</ac>		<strength></strength>		<stealth></stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Sentinel Shield</name>		<type>S</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>	While holding this shield, you have advantage on initiative rolls and Wisdom (Perception) checks. The shield is emblazoned with a symbol of an eye.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 199</text>		<ac>2</ac>		<strength></strength>		<stealth></stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Shield of Missile Attraction</name>		<type>S</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	While holding this shield, you have resistance to damage from ranged weapon attacks.</text>		<text></text>		<text>Curse: This shield is cursed. Attuning to it curses you until you are targeted by the remove curse spell or similar magic. Removing the shield fails to end the curse on you. Whenever a ranged weapon attack is made against a target within 10 feet of you, the curse causes you to become the target instead.</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 200</text>		<ac>2</ac>		<strength></strength>		<stealth></stealth>	</item>
	<item>		<name>Spellguard Shield</name>		<type>S</type>		<weight>6</weight>		<text>Requires Attunement</text>		<text>	While holding this shield, you have advantage on saving throws against spells and other magical effects, and spell attacks have disadvantage against you</text>		<text />		<text>Source: Dungeon Master's Guide p. 201</text>		<ac>2</ac>		<strength></strength>		<stealth></stealth>	</item>
</compendium>
